The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
♪ Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano ♪
The dreams I see are my secret
♪ Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano ♪
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
♪ Akai manto hira hira ♪
A red cape fluttering
♪ Uma o tobasu oujo ♪
Galloping on a horse—the princess
♪ Sore ga atashi ♪
That’s me!
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Ribon no kishi wa ♪
The Knight of the Ribbon,
♪ Honto wa hontto wa ♪
Truly, truly,
♪ Atashi nano sa ♪
It’s really me!
Forty-Eighth Episode
The Bounty
Sapphire that Disappeared into the Sea
It's me.
Silence!
Gentlemen, if you want to make a million yen, listen up!
A million yen?
A million yen!
You know the princess of Silverland.
You mean Sapphire?
That's right. Go kidnap Sapphire. Don't kill her. Just bring her to me.
What for?
I won't answer questions.
A one-million-yen reward to whoever brings her by tomorrow morning.
Tonight, the castle's back gate is unguarded and unlocked.
Good luck, gentlemen.
Hey, a million yen!
That pays better than being pirates.
Count me in.
It's quiet... Too quiet!
On a night like this, I feel like something bad is about to happen...
Oh, Lord Sapphire, is something wrong?
Oh, it's just you, Doctor Uranai!
It is far too quiet, Lord Sapphire.
I was just thinking the same thing.
In the hallway on my way here...
Not a single guard was standing watch.
Not a single one?
Guards!
Are there no guards here?
Will this really work?
It's my master plan. Just watch!
Looks like the bounty is ours.
Who are you?
Who are you, showing up after us?
Get them!
We won't let you steal our bounty!
Hurry up!
You can leave the rest to us.
She's sound asleep.
Sapphire, you're awake?
I knew you'd show up.
Who are you?
Since you're awake, we're doing this the rough way!
Just get into this sack quietly!
Blood! Is that you, Blood?
It's Boss Blood! Did you come for the bounty, too?
Boss! Trying to hog it all for yourself?
Thank you! But why are you here...? What bounty?
Give me the reward for Sapphire as promised.
It's definitely Sapphire...
Here's my one million yen reward!
Where am I?
Oh, Blood!
Wait, do you know each other?
Why did you hit me all of a sudden?
And who on earth are these people?
No way. Don't address me so casually, Princess of Silverland. It's annoying.
Blood!
Now that I've got what I came for, I'm done here. See ya.
Blood, wait!
Wait, wait—you're staying right here.
What?
What on earth is going on?
What happened?
Hang in there for three days.
Three days?
What's with this explosion?!
There's something at the bottom of the sea.
This is incredible!
Listen up, everyone! The explosion test was a success!
Transport all the finished gunpowder to
Silverland's castle town by tomorrow night!
The day after tomorrow—
the afternoon of the third day—
we'll detonate the gunpowder and blow the city of Silverland to pieces!
Now everyone, keep making more of this top-grade gunpowder!
How's that? Looks just like the real decree, doesn't it?
Anyone would take it for real.
Once this is posted, Sapphire takes all the blame!
Precisely!
What does it say?
A grand amusement park shall be built for the children.
All obstructing buildings will be demolished.
Disobeyers will be executed immediately.
From Princess Sapphire?!
Our homes...
How cruel...
Is this really Princess Sapphire's order?
Execution? Isn't that a bit extreme for an amusement park?
What in the world is Princess Sapphire thinking?
Sapphire!
Who's calling me?
That was definitely Blood's voice!
Quiet.
It sounds noisy outside. What's going on?
Lord Goll, this man was loitering in front of Sapphire's room.
You're...
Yep, it's me! Pirate Blood!
Whoa, boss, hold on!
Pirating wasn't paying off, so I snuck in here to change careers!
Cut me some slack!
Hey!
Bring out Sapphire!
X!
So you really are part of the X-Union!
What evil scheme are you plotting, bringing me here?!
Just as the rumors say, she's quite feisty.
Hey, Sapphire, do you know this man?
Blood!
Still, I'm glad you found this place.
I really thought you'd betrayed me.
Hey, how many times do I have to tell you?
I don't know you. You've got the wrong guy.
I can't get anything done with you butting in. Now back off! What a pain.
Blood!
I can't believe Blood would betray me after how close we were...
Something terrible is happening...
Someone! Open this door!
Let me out!
Princess of Silverland or not,
I don't care about any of that.
All I want is money.
Fine, alright.
You seem like you could be useful.
Hey, take this guy to the workshop.
Well? Learned your lesson yet?
Hey, this is crazy!
X-Union isn't naive enough to trust you.
You can stay like that all night.
This is just going too far!
I'm not listening to anything Sapphire says anymore!
Everyone! Poor people of Silverland!
You have every right to be angry!
Out of nowhere, Princess Sapphire declared
she's tearing down the castle town in three days to build
a children's amusement park here.
What's gotten into her?
But as long as Princess Sapphire's decree stands,
we must obey her orders.
What a terrible person Sapphire is!
Nylon did a fine job.
The gunpowder arrives this afternoon, and the town will be blown to bits.
And X-Union storms into a desperate Silverland.
Grand Duke Duralumin.
Well, well, Your Majesty.
Did Sapphire really order the town to be demolished?
Yes, that's right.
Apparently, she refuses to leave until construction is finished and
she's been running all over the site.
To think she'd do such a thing...
I can't believe this.
What could have happened?
Sapphire, please hurry back...
Someone! Someone open this door!
Will Silverland be alright?
Father,
Mother,
please forgive me for being so helpless.
Open the undersea tunnel!
Deliver the gunpowder to Silverland within the hour!
Let's go!
Silverland won't go down that easily!
Who threw dynamite into the room?
Sapphire, are you okay?
Blood!
You came to save me.
Of course I did.
Are you hurt, Sapphire?
X-Union is about to blow Silverland to bits with dynamite!
What?
But how do we get out of here?
Don't let Blood get away!
Feed him to the sharks!
Hurry up and search! Quick!
Over here!
Look, over there!
Sapphire is with him, too!
Get them!
So Blood was just putting on an act to uncover the X-Union's true motive!
That's right. He did it all for your sake.
Listen, Sapphire!
Take this cart straight to Silverland and stop the explosion!
Blood, what about you?
Don't worry about me.
Just save Silverland, alright?
I'm sorry, Blood.
What, you still haven't found them?
Search! Search, hurry!
Goll! Over here! Over here!
Heads up!
Hey, you so-called X-Union!
I, the great Blood, am more than enough for the likes of you!
I won't let you get your hands on Sapphire!
Come on, bring it on!
What are you doing?! Catch him, quick!
Go! Attack!
Sapphire! Run! Hurry!
Whoa, isn't that dynamite?!
Oh no! They're gonna blow up our houses with that!
Let me... Lord Nylon, the dynamite is all set.
Alright, soldiers! Light every last bit of gunpowder in town!
Look! It's Sapphire!
Get her!
Damn it!
We have to hurry, or something terrible will happen!
Ah! Sapphire is cutting the fuses!
Wait, wasn't it Sapphire who gave the signal?!
Huh? What? Sapphire... Sapphire is...
Nylon! On whose orders did you do this?!
Well, an official decree was issued in Lord Sapphire's name...
A decree from me...?
Sapphire!
Looks like you managed to prevent the explosion!
Blood! You're safe!
Of course I am!
Everyone!
Setting the explosives was the work of the X-Union!
Come on! Let's take down those X-Union bastards!
Get 'em!
Hey!
Lord Sapphire, what about me?
Stay right there until your name is cleared!
You can't be serious...
We've got trouble!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Stop!
Come back and fight!
Damn it!
They escaped in the cart!
What a pathetic bunch!
Amazing!
Just look at it plow right into them, Sapphire!
What on earth happened? I don't hear the explosions anymore.
W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-What is this earthquake?!
What was that earthquake just now?
An underwater explosion sank the island.
Oh, what a disaster! All our hard work, down the drain...
Lord Sapphire!
Thank you. Thanks to you, the town was spared from destruction.
It's too early to celebrate.
The X-Union is finally closing in on Silverland.
But no matter what happens everyone,
we must protect our nation, this beautiful Silverland!
Let us all join forces!
Just as Sapphire predicted, the main force of the X-Union turned its dark fangs toward Silverland.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen ♪
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
♪ Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen ♪
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
♪ Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo ♪
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
♪ tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai ♪
Our bonded hearts will never part.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP